franchisehelp.com 2015-09-22

# Terms of Service & Privacy Policy for Franchise Help

**Privacy Policy**

 **Effective Date:   06/27/2014**

This privacy policy applies to [www.franchisehelp.com](https://www.franchisehelp.com/) owned and operated by FranchiseHelp Holdings, LLC (Henceforward “Franchise Help” “We” “Us”). This privacy policy describes how Franchise Help collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site.    It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

FranchiseHelp Holdings, LLC has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.franchisehelp.com](https://www.franchisehelp.com/).

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions _. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at_[ _support@franchisehelp.com_](mailto:support@franchisehelp.com) _.   _If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

 **1.   ****  Information Collection and Use**

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address

  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password

  * Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences

We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order

  * Pass your information on to the businesses you have requested

  * Send you an order confirmation

  * Assess your needs to determine suitable products

  * Send you requested product or service information

  * Respond to customer service requests

  * Send you a newsletter

  * Send you marketing communications

  * Respond to your questions and concerns

  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts

  *  _User Data Supplementation_

We obtain address information about you from third party sources, such _as LeadQC, to verify your contact information to prevent fraud._

 **2.   ****Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.  

Based on your expressed interest in the franchise opportunities we provide, when you request additional information about a particular opportunity we share your personal information with those companies so they can contact you directly.  In cases where we do not have direct relationships with a franchise owner, we may share your contact information with franchise consultants.   If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at [support@franchisehelp.com](mailto:support@franchisehelp.com)

  *  _Service Providers_

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing payments or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us.

  *  _Legal Disclaimer_

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

  * if FranchiseHelp Holdings, LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

 **3.   ****  User Access and Choice**

If your personally information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may contact us by emailing our Customer Support at [support@franchisehelp.com](mailto:support@franchisehelp.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.  We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

  *  _Opt-out Preferences_

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [support@franchisehelp.com](mailto:support@franchisehelp.com)

 **4.   ****Tracking Technologies / Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes.  We use cookies on this site.  We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

We set a persistent cookie to enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

  *  _Web Beacons / Gifs_

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

  *  _Analytics / Log Files_

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

  *  _3rd Party Tracking_

The use of cookies by our affiliates and service providers is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.  Our third party affiliates may also employ clear gifs images, and scripts that help them better manage their content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information.

  *  _Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting_

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here <http://preferences.truste.com/>.  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

 ** _You may also opt-out through this link:  <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>_**

We use Google AdSense to publish ads on this site.  When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites.   You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**5.   ****  Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [support@franchisehelp.com](mailto:support@franchisehelp.com)

 **6.   ****  Additional Information**

  *  _Links to 3rd Party Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Franchise Help.   If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

  *  _Blog / Forum_

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. _To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at_[support@franchisehelp.com](mailto:support@franchisehelp.com).  In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

  *  _Testimonials_

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [support@franchisehelp.com](mailto:support@franchisehelp.com). 

  *  _Social Media Widgets_

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as Facebook and Twitter Widgets (interactive mini-programs that run on our site). These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

  *  _Changes To This Policy_

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

 **7.   ****   Contact Us**

FranchiseHelp Holdings LLC  
57 E 11th St, Suite 3A  
New York, NY 10003  
Phone: 646-419-4365

For questions, comments, and support, email:  
support@franchisehelp.com
